Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Other NYFA Programs, 1970-2010; 45 linear feet in 45 record cartons
  - Subseries E. Community Assets, 1993-2005; 13 linear feet
    - Community Assets - Bargemusic, Ltd., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Community Assets - Battery Dance Company, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Community Assets - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Community Assets - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Community Assets - Big Apple Performing Arts, Inc., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Community Assets - Bloomingdale House of Music, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Community Assets - Boys Harbor, Inc., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Community Assets - Bread and Roses Cultural Project, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Community Assets - Bronx Arts Ensemble, Inc., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Community Assets - Bronx Dance Theatre, Inc., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Community Assets - Bronx Opera Company, Inc., 1998 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Community Assets - Bronx River Arts Center and Gallery, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Community Assets - The Brooklyn Arts Council, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Community Assets - The Children's Art Carnival, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Community Assets - Circum-Arts Foundation, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Community Assets - City Lights Youth Theatre, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Community Assets - City Lore, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Community Assets - City Parks Foundation, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Community Assets - CityArts, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Community Assets - Community Works, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Community Assets - Creative Arts Workshop For kids, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Community Assets - Creative Time, Inc., 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Community Assets - Dance Ring, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Community Assets - DanceSpace Project, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Community Assets - Dominican Womens' Development Center, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Community Assets - Downtown Community Television Centr, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Community Assets - Drawing Center, Inc., 1997 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Community Assets - DTV Productions, Ltd., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Community Assets - Earth Celebrations, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Community Assets - El Puente of Williamsburg, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Community Assets - The Eldridge Street Project, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Community Assets - The Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Community Assets - Flushing Council on Culture and the Arts, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Community Assets - Folksbiene Yiddish Theater, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Community Assets - A Gathering of the Tribes, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Community Assets - Africa Arts Theatre Company, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Community Assets - African Voices Communications, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Community Assets - African Voices Communications, Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Community Assets - Afterdark CATV Productions, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Community Assets - The Alliance of Queens Artists, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Community Assets - Opera Musical Theatre Company, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Community Assets - The American Spanish Dance Theater, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Community Assets - Art Resources for Teachers and Students, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Community Assets - Association for Development of Multiethnic Relationship, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Community Assets - Black American Heritage Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Community Assets - The Brooklyn Philharmonic Chorus, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Community Assets - Bronx Symphony Orchestra, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Community Assets - Caribbean-American Repretory Theatre, Inc., 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Community Assets - American Sports and Cultural Youth Movement, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Community Assets - Catanach Ballet Theater, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Community Assets - Center for Thanatology Research and Education, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Community Assets - The Chinese Music Ensemble of Network, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Community Assets - City Island Arts Organization, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Community Assets - Colloquium Contemporary Dance Company, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Community Assets - Communicacion Y Relaciones Fundacion Dialogo Cultural (CORFUDICUL), 1997 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Community Assets - Communicacion Y Relaciones Fundacion Dialogo Cultural (CORFUDICUL), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Community Assets - Dance Across Borders, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Community Assets - Dance Film Association, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Community Assets - Drumsongs Productions, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Community Assets - Percussion Group, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Community Assets - Flo-Bert, Ltd., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Community Assets - Gallery Players, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Community Assets - Girl and Co., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Community Assets - Gold Mountain Institute for Traditional Shadow Theatre, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Community Assets - Gold Mountain Institute for Traditional Shadow Theatre, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Community Assets - Harlem Theatre Company, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Community Assets - The Heights Players, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Community Assets - High Tides Dance, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Community Assets - Hispanic Organization of Latin Actors, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Community Assets - The Hudson Guild, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Community Assets - inCollaboration, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Community Assets - IDEAS, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Community Assets - Jackson Heights Arts Club, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Community Assets - Jackson Heights Arts Club, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Community Assets - Jazz Legacy, Inc., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Community Assets - Kurdish Heritage Foundation of Americas, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Community Assets - Labryinth, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Community Assets - Learning By Design, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Community Assets - Longwood Arts Project, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Community Assets - Long Island Conservatory Theatre, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Community Assets - Langor Ebony Ensemble, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Community Assets - Mass Transit Street Theater, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Community Assets - Manhattan Graphics Center, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Community Assets - Morning Star Full Gospel Assembly, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Community Assets - Multicultural Music Group, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Community Assets - Media Alliance, Inc., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Community Assets - MusicInn Studios, Inc., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Community Assets - Report on Cultural Diversity of Arts and Cultural Organizations, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Community Assets - Fellowships Information and promotional Material Including Booklets, Flyers, and Brochures, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Community Assets - Promotional Material including Printed Booklets, Brochures, and Flyers, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Community Assets - Annual Report (FY 91, 93, 95), 1991-1995 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Community Assets - The New York Lesbian and Gay Experimental Film Festival, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Community Assets - Council for Cultural Affairs, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Community Assets - Annabella Gonzales Dance Theatre, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Community Assets - Arts and Cultural Program at Flusihing YMCA, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Community Assets - Annabella Gonzales Dance Theatre, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Community Assets - Annabella Gonzales Dance Theatre, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Community Assets - YWCA Flushing Branch, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Community Assets - Brooklyn WaterFront Artists Coalition, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Community Assets - Brooklyn WaterFront Artists Coalition, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Community Assets - Center for Korean-American Culture, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Community Assets - Center for Korean-American Culture, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Community Assets - Centro Culture Orlando Martinez, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Community Assets - Centro Culture Orlando Martinez, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Community Assets - Chinese Theatre Works, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Community Assets - Chinese Theatre Workshop, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Community Assets - Chinese Theatre Workshop, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Community Assets - Chinese Theatre Workshop, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Community Assets - Exceterica, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Community Assets - The National Book Foundation, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Community Assets - Groupo Bridges, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Community Assets - Groupo Bridges, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Community Assets - Global Action Project, Inc., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Community Assets - Global Action Project, Inc., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Community Assets - Global Action Project, Inc., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Community Assets - Great Small Works, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Community Assets - Great Small Works, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Community Assets - Great Small Works, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Community Assets - Great Small Works, Glückel von Hameln, Promotional Information, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Community Assets - Hudson Waterfront Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Community Assets - Hudson Waterfront Museum, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Community Assets - Hudson Waterfront Museum, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Community Assets - Latea (Latin American Theater Experiment), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Community Assets - Voice and Vision, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Community Assets - YARA Arts Group, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Community Assets - YARA Arts Group, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Community Assets - YARA Arts Group, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Community Assets - YARA Arts Group, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Community Assets - Brooklyn Youth Chorus, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Community Assets - Brooklyn Youth Chorus, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Community Assets - Brooklyn Youth Chorus, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Community Assets - YARA Arts Group, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Community Assets - COAHSI, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Community Assets - COAHSI, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Community Assets - Cultural Coalition of Staten Island, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Community Assets - Dixon Place, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Community Assets - Dixon Place, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Community Assets - Dixon Place, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Community Assets - Elders Share the Arts, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Community Assets - Elders Share the Arts, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Community Assets - Elders Share the Arts, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Community Assets - Elders Share the Arts, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Community Assets - Museum of Chinese In the Americas, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Community Assets - Museum of Chinese In the Americas, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Community Assets - Museum of Chinese In the Americas, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Community Assets - Latea (Latin American Theater Experiment) Rating Sheets from Panelists, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Community Assets - La Plaza Cultural, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Community Assets - Plaza Culutral, 1977-2003 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Community Assets - Cultural Plaza, 1977-2003 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Community Assets - Pepation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Community Assets - Latino Experimental Fantastic Theatre, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Community Assets - Latino Experimental Fantastic Theatre, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Community Assets - Oratorio Society of Queens, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Community Assets - Oratorio Society of Queens, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Community Assets - Smack Mellon Studios, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Community Assets - Socrates Sculpture Park, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Community Assets - Young Korean-American Service Education Center, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Community Assets - Pepation, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Community Assets - Pepation, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Community Assets - Third World Newsreel, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Community Assets - Third World Newsreel, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Community Assets - Volunteer Lawyers In The Arts, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Community Assets - Volunteer Lawyers In The Arts, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Community Assets - 600 BC E. 9th St. Block Association, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Community Assets - 600 BC E. 9th St. Block Association, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Community Assets - 600 BC E. 9th St. Block Association/Viva La Plaza!, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Community Assets - America's Vocal Ensemble, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Community Assets - America's Vocal Ensemble, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Community Assets - Angels of Music Harmony, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Community Assets - Angels of Music Harmony, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Community Assets - Flaminco Latino, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Community Assets - Flaminco Latino, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Community Assets - Latino Experimental Fantastic Theatre (LEFT), 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Community Assets - American-Indian Artists, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Community Assets - Amerinda (American-Indian Artists), 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Community Assets - Cherry Tree Association, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Community Assets - Cherry Tree Association, Inc., 2000 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Community Assets - Deep Dish TV, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Community Assets - DykeTV, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Community Assets - DTV Productions, Ltd., 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Community Assets - Infinity Dance Theatre, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Community Assets - La Troupe McKandal, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Community Assets - Promote Art Works/The Micro Museum, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Community Assets - The MicroMuseum, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Community Assets - The MicroMuseum, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Community Assets - New 600 BC East 9th Street Block and Neighborhood Association, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Community Assets - Promote Art Works, Inc., 2001 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Community Assets - New Radio and Performing Arts Center, 2000-2003 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Community Assets - The Raj Kumari Cultural Center Booster Grant, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Community Assets - The Raj Kumari Cultural Center, Inc., 2000 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Community Assets - The Raj Kumari Cultural Center, Inc., 2002 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Community Assets - The Raj Kumari Cultural Center, Inc., 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Community Assets - REPOHistory, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Community Assets - Sandy Ground Historical Society, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Community Assets - Sandy Ground Historical Society, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Community Assets - Seasoned Citizens Theatre Company, Inc., 1998 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Community Assets - Seasoned Citizens Theatre Company, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Community Assets - Seasoned Citizens Theatre Company, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Community Assets - Smack Mellon Studios, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Community Assets - Smack Mellon Studios, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Community Assets - Smack Mellon Studios, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Community Assets - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Community Assets - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Community Assets - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Community Assets - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Community Assets - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Community Assets - Creative Alternatives of New York, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Community Assets - Creative Alternatives of New York, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Community Assets - Creative Alternatives of New York, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Community Assets - Socrates Sculpture Park, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Community Assets - Socrates Sculpture Park, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Community Assets - Socrates Sculpture Park, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Community Assets - Theater By The Blind Corp., 2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Community Assets - Theater By The Blind Corp., 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Community Assets - Theater By The Blind Corp., 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Community Assets - Voice and Vision, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Community Assets - REPOHistory, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Community Assets - Lower East Side Printshop, Inc., 2001 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Community Assets - Lower East Side Printshop, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Community Assets - Lower East Side Printshop, Inc., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Community Assets - New York Lesbian and Gay Experiemental Film/Video Festival, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Community Assets - Music From China, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Community Assets - Music From China, 1997-1999 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Community Assets - Other Countries, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Community Assets - Other Countries, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Community Assets - Paper Tiger Television, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Community Assets - Paper Tiger Television, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Community Assets - PAX Theater Community, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Community Assets - PAX Theater Community, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Community Assets - Young Dancers in Repertory, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Community Assets - Foundation for Children and The Classics, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Community Assets - Foundation for Independent Video and Film, Inc., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Community Assets - Foundry Theater, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Community Assets - Franklin Furnace Archive, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Community Assets - Gateway Symphony Staten Island, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Community Assets - Grosvenor Neighborhood House, Inc., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Community Assets - Hands on Sign Interpreted Performances, Inc., 1999 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Community Assets - Risa Jaroslow and Dancers (HighTide Dance, Inc.), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Community Assets - Hispanic Young Peoples' Alternatives, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Community Assets - Home for Contemporary Theatre and Art, Ltd., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Community Assets - Housing Works, Inc., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Community Assets - International Agency for Minority Artists Affairs, Inc., 1998 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Community Assets - International Agency for Minority Artists Affairs, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Community Assets - The Irish Repertory Theatre, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Community Assets - Issanu Noguchi Garden Museum, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Community Assets - Jacques Marchais Museum of Tibetan Art, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Community Assets - Jazzmobile, Inc., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Community Assets - King Manor Association of Long Island, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Community Assets - Lehman College Art Gallery, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Community Assets - Lotus Fine Arts Productions, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Community Assets - Los Pleneros de la 21, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Community Assets - Lower East Side Tenement Museum, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Community Assets - Mabou Mines Development Foundation, Inc., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Community Assets - Manna House Workshops, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Community Assets - Builders Creative Arts Co., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Community Assets - Movement Research Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Community Assets - Negro Ensemble Company, Inc., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Community Assets - Network of Cultural Center of Color, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Community Assets - New Federal Theatre, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Community Assets - New Festival, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Community Assets - The New Music Consort, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Community Assets - Plays for Living, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Community Assets - The Point Community Development, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Community Assets - Pregones Theater, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Community Assets - Primary Stages Company, Inc., 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Community Assets - The Printmaking Workshop, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Community Assets - Soundance, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Community Assets - Spanish Dance Arts Company, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Community Assets - StoreFront In Art and Architechture, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Community Assets - Target MarginTheater, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Community Assets - Creative Arts Lab/Teachers College-Columbia University, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Community Assets - Teatro Circulo, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Community Assets - Thalia Spanish Theatre, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Community Assets - Thalia Spanish Theatre, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Community Assets - Turtle Bay Music School, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Community Assets - Volunteer Consulting Group, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Community Assets - Williamsburg Art and Historical Center, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Community Assets - The Wooster Group, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Community Assets - The Working Theatre Company, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Community Assets - York Theatre Company, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Community Assets - YMCA Beacon Center, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Community Assets - Quintet of the Americas, Inc., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Community Assets - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Community Assets - October 24th, 1996 Meeting (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Community Assets - Advisory Committee Development and Recommendations, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Community Assets - Code of Ethics Form, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Community Assets - General Program Information, Meetings, Agendas, Description, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Community Assets - Advisory Committee Information, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Community Assets - Citizens Committee for NYC, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Community Assets - The Arts and Business Council, Mentoring Programs, Correspondence, General Information, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Community Assets - Reunion Reports, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 44)